NGOC-PHU LE

Al Engineer

@ lephu0803@gmail.com

**** +84 859-256-159

♀ Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

in linkedin.com/in/lephu96

ABOUT ME

I am a studious person who is eager to learn new things and ready to face of challenges. About one year working as an AI Engineer in industrial environment, I have obtained much experience in analyzing image data and handling issues by applying Computer Vision and Machine Learning knowledge. Now, I would like get in-depth and comprehensively understand the data instead of giving a try or depending on the state-of-the-art Deep Learning algorithms and fine-tuning the model without looking back the data. Therefore, I am seeking for a Data Scientist position to strengthen my working skills in Data Science, Machine Learning. Also, I would like to contribute my abilities to the company and my working team.

EXPERIENCES

Al Engineer

GE3F Pte. Ltd

Hang. 2018 - Present

♥ Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

- Researched and developed application for detecting defect on semiconductor and component using Computer Vision and Deep Learning.
- Researched and implemented Generative Adversarial Networks (GANs) to generate images, researched method to evaluate GANs model.
- Trained and fine-tuned deep learning models for defected contact lens classification.

Al Project Intern

Cinnamon AI Labs

Marg. 2017 - Nov. 2017

♥ Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

 Project: Visualize summary tool for Slack chat Used Machine learning and Deep learning for clustering unread message.

PROJECTS

- Fashion Image Retrieval, Swiss Innovation Challenge 2018
 Used Computer Vision and Deep Learning for extract image information to image embedding.

 Applied Vector Quantization for storing image data and search.
- Undergraduate Thesis: Smart Advertising System
 Designed the system using Computer Vision and Deep
 Learning for extracting age, gender, watching time of customer
 who facing and watching the digital advertisement board.
 Used parallel programming to improve the processing speed of
 the system.

Used flask to design API for tranfering data between client and server.

AWARD AND SCHOLARSHIPS

- Incentive Award in Eureka Scientific Research Students Awards 2018.
- First prize in Intelligent Program 2017 for best project at program's final contest.
- Intelligent Program Scholarship 2017 by Cinnamon Al Labs Vietnam for Machine Learning training course.
- TAKAKO Vietnam Co., Ltd Scholarship 2017 for Excellent Student.

SKILLS

- Programming Language: Python, C/C++, C#.
- Framework, library: Tensorflow, Keras, scikit-learn, pandas, numpy, flask, multiprocessing
- Machine Learning, Deep learning: Linear regression, Logistic regression, SVM, Decision Tree, CNN, RNN, GAN,...

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering in Mechatronics, Robotics

University of Technology annd Education

2014 - 2018

♥ Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

PUBLICATION

Le Anh Tran and Ngoc Phu Le and Truong Dong Do and My Ha Le, A Vision-based Method for Autonomous Landing on a Target with a Quadcopter, 4th International Conference on Green Technology and Sustainable Development (GTSD), 2018